
Deck.create(name: "Banana Slug Trivia", cards: [
Card.create(question: "The french dude", answer: "Quentin"),
Card.create(question: "The wizard", answer: "Topher"),
Card.create(question: "The tall guy", answer: "Tim"),
Card.create(question: "Papa Poison", answer: "Stephen"),
Card.create(question: "Glenn", answer: "Matthew"),
Card.create(question: "Mozzarella", answer: "Brittany"),
Card.create(question: "Cool first name", answer: "Strand"),
Card.create(question: "Tsunami", answer: "Johnny"),
Card.create(question: "*insert meow here*", answer: "Rao Rao"),
Card.create(question: "Sweet awesomeness", answer: "Shadi"),
Card.create(question: "Led Zepplin", answer: "Phil"),
Card.create(question: "Apparently a god of pool", answer: "Sherif"),
Card.create(question: "Thinks farting is hilarious", answer: "Armando"),
Card.create(question: "Our home", answer: "Dev Bootcamp"),
Card.create(question: "Cookie Monster", answer: "Quentin"),
Card.create(question: "Most important post punk of all time", answer: "Joy Division"),
Card.create(question: "The king of algorithms", answer: "Hunter"),
Card.create(question: "The guy who runs on linux", answer: "Ivan"),
Card.create(question: "El don", answer: "Jose"),
Card.create(question: "Our biggest loss", answer: "Erin"),
Card.create(question: "Fucking...", answer:"Steve"),
Card.create(question: "Secretly loves country music", answer:"Jamie"),
Card.create(question: "Gives the best Lightning talks ever", answer:"Jamie"),
Card.create(question: "Meatballs...", answer:"Chris")
])


Deck.create(name: "Urban Dictionary Trivia", cards: [Card.create(question: "you only live once, might as well make it tasty", answer: "yolowmit"),
Card.create(question: "Taking on the night life after taking care of business during the day.", answer: "going batman"),
Card.create(question: "Sex only on Anniversaries, Birthdays and Christmas", answer: "abc sex"),
Card.create(question: "A word spawned by combining bro with another word", answer: "portmanbro"),
Card.create(question: "a phrase used at the end of a story that had really no point to be told to someone", answer: "and then i found five dollars"),
Card.create(question: "A threelationship; a relationship with three partners", answer: "throuple"),
Card.create(question: "When you put a beer bottle in your mouth, and keep your mouth wrapped around it all day.", answer: "mouth hugging")])